Dorothy Kenyon Papers, 1850-1998
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES V. LEGAL PRACTICE (1936-1969)
  - Research Files
    - The Investigation of the Magistrates' Court in the First Judicial Department and the Magistrates thereof, and of attorneys-at-law practicing in said Courts regarding Magistrate Jean H. Norris: opinions and report of Samuel Seabury, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Petitition to the Congress on behalf of certain Married Women Formerly Employed in the NYC Post Office by New York League of Women Voters, 1934 (Box 25)
    - Hearings before the Committee on Military Affairs, House of Representatives, 78th Congress on S. 495, a Bill to establish a Women's Army Corps for Service in the Army of the U.S., 1943 (Box 25)
    - Eugene Dennis, et al., v. U.S.A., Supreme Court of the United States: supplemental petition for rehearing (by George W. Crockett, Jr., Richard Gladstein, Abraham J. Isserman, Louis F. McCabe, Harry Sacher), 1951 (Box 25)
    - Elza Leslye Jackson, et al., v. U.S.A., U.S. Court of Appeals, 5th Circuit: printed record, 1964 [see box 26] (Box 25)
    - Thelma Bowe, et al., v. Colgate Palmolive Company, U.S. District Court, Southern District of Indiana, New Albany Division: memorandum by Herbert Segal, David E. Feller, Jerry D. Anker, Counsel for Local 14, International Chemical Workers Union for Local 15 International Chemical Workers Union), 1966 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Joint Anti-Fascist Refugee Committee v. Tom C. Clark, Attorney General of the U.S. et al., U.S. Court of Appeals, District of Columbia Circuit: amicus curiae brief (by American Civil Liberties Union), n.d. (Box 25)
    - Elza Lesly Jackson, et al. v. U.S.A., U.S. Court of Appeals, 5th Circuit: printed record, 1964 (Box 26)
- SERIES VI. ACTIVITIES AND ORGANIZATIONS (1923-1971)
  - Abortion Rights Association of New York: correspondence, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Academy of Political Science: correspondence, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Human Rights: correspondence, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - American Association for the United Nations: clippings, printed material, and correspondence, 1945-66 (Box 27, Folder 4-5)
  - American Association of University Women
    - General: clippings and printed material, 1947-55, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Massachusetts division: newsletter, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - New York division: correspondence, 1951-68 (Box 27, Folder 8-10)
  - American Bar Association: correspondence and printed material, 1950-60 s (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - American Branch of the International Law Association: correspondence, 1965-70 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - American Civil Liberties Union, [see also SERIES V--LEGAL PRACTICE]
    - General: printed material, 1949-65 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence
      - General
        - 1949-69 (Box 28, Folder 2-10)
        - 1970-71 (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
      - Individuals
        - Catherine East, 1966-69 (Box 29, Folder 3)
        - Dorothy Height, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 4)
        - Mary Dublin Keyserling, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 5)
        - Corliss Lamont, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 6)
        - Constance Baker Motley, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 7)
        - Pauli Murray, 1966-71 (Box 29, Folder 8)
        - Eleanor Holmes Norton, 1966-68 (Box 29, Folder 9)
        - Esther Peterson, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 10)
        - Harriet Pilpel, 1965-71 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Board of Directors: biographies of members, minutes, 1954-71, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 12-13)
    - Committees
      - Selection of Judges: lists, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 14)
      - Constitution: correspondence and report, 1968-70 (Box 29, Folder 15)
      - Due Process: agendas, correspondence, and minutes, 1956, 1960, 1965, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 16)
      - Equality
        - General: correspondence, lists, minutes, newspaper clippings, notes, and printed material, 1965-69 (Box 29, Folder 17)
        - Issues
          - Collection and Dissemination of Race Data by the Government: correspondence, minutes, proposals, and statements, 1961-67 (Box 29, Folder 18)
          - Discrimination in Private Organizations: correspondence, minutes, and statements, 1955-66 (Box 30, Folder 1)
          - Equal Rights Amendment: correspondence, minutes, and proposals, 1959-70, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 2)
          - Quotas and Compensatory treatment: agendas, correspondence, minutes, printed material, statements, and typescripts (by Pauli Murray and unidentified authors), 1963-67, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Ethics: report, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Executive: memorandum, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - International Civil Liberties: minutes, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Special Committee on 1940 Resolution: correspondence, minutes, notes, and printed material, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Conferences: programs, 1947-70, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Publicity: clippings, 1951-69, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Policy Guide, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Subjects
      - Abortion: correspondence, minutes, newspaper clippings, notes, policy statements, and printed material, 1967-70, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Biennial Convention of 1968: remarks by DK, report, and speech ("Civil Liberties and the War on Crime" by Harriet Pilpel), 1968 (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Bill of Rights: printed matter and publicity, 1955-60 (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - Church-State: correspondence and magazine clipping, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - Collection and Use of Data on Race, Religion or National Origin: correspondence, minutes, research material, and resolutions, 1958-61, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 15)
      - Communism: printed material, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 16)
      - Equal Rights Amendment: correspondence, notes, printed material, and typescripts (by Kenyon, and Kenyon with Pauli Murray), 1953-71, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 17)
      - Integration: reports and speeches, 1956-63 (Box 30, Folder 18)
      - Internal Security: transcripts of Congressional testimony by Ernest Angell, 1955 and Hope Eastman, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 19)
      - Police authority: speech by Bernard Weisberg, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 20)
      - Race exclusion in state courts
        - Press release, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 21)
        - White v. Cook: briefs, correspondence, decree, notes, publicity, and writ of injunction, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 1-4)
        - Willis v. Carson: complaint, 1966 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Sex discrimination
        - General: bills, correspondence, memoranda, notes, proposals (by Kenyon and Pauli Murray), and publicity, 1961-70 (Box 31, Folder 6)
        - Education: Kirstein et al. v. University of Virginia, U.S. District Court, 1970? (Box 31, Folder 7)
        - Inheritance: Sally Reed v. Cecil Reed, U.S. Supreme Court, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 8)
        - Jury Service: briefs, correspondence, documents, memoranda (by Kenyon and Pauli Murray), newspaper clippings, notes, and printed material, 1935, 1954, 1961, 1966-71, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 1-3)
        - Veterans Preference Act: memoranda and notes, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 4)
        - Speech and protest (Box 32)
      - Coffin, Ferber, Goodman, Raskin & Spock v. U.S.A.: indictment, magazine clippings, minutes, notes, and, publicity, 1963-68 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Wiretapping: correspondence, minutes, notes, and reports 1961, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - American Committee for Democracy and Intellectual Freedom: correspondence, 1940, [see also McCarthy Hearings] (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - American Council on Education: program, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - American-European Friendship Association: programs, 1963-64 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - American Federation of Labor-Council of Industrial Organzations: correspondence, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - American Friends of the Middle East: correspondence, newspaper clippings, and printed material, 1953-1969 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - American Institute of Banking: printed material, 1948-49 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - American Jewish Congress: correspondence, programs, and printed material, 1952-59 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - American Labor Party: correspondence, newspaper clippings, and publicity, 1939, [see also McCarthy Hearings] (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - American Middle East Rehabilitation: correspondence, minutes, and reports, 1964-70 (Box 33, Folder 9-10)
  - American Near East Refugee Aid, Inc.: correspondence, 1970-71 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - American Women's Association: printed material, 1950-51, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Americans for Democratic Action: correspondence, newspaper clippings, printed material, and reports, 1950-71 (Box 33, Folder 13-15)
  - Americans for Public Schools: correspondence, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Ansonia Independent Democrats: correspondence and program, 1964, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Association for Humane Abortion: correspondence, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Association for the Study of Abortion, Inc: correspondence, 1967-70 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Association for Voluntary Sterilization: correspondence, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Baldwin School: conference program, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Brooklyn Academy of Music: catalog, 1961-62 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences: printed material, 1944-45 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters: correspondence, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Business and Professional Women: correspondence, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - C.A.F.E.: correspondence, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions: correspondence, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Chelsea Action Center: agendas, correspondence, minutes, proposals, and reports, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Chelsea Against the Stolport: correspondence, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Chelsea Area Program Committee: correspondence, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Chelsea Citizens Committee for the All-Day Neighborhood School: printed material, 1957, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Chelsea Civil Rights Council: bylaws, correspondence, minutes, and printed material, 1963-67, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Chelsea Committee for Family Planning: correspondence, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Chelsea Committee for Neighborhood Development, [see Lower West Side Community Development Activities] (Box 34)
  - Chelsea Historic District Council: correspondence, 1969-70 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Chelsea Independent Anti-Poverty Action Committee, [see Lower West Side Community Development Activities] (Box 34)
  - Chelsea Meetings for Community Unity, Inc.: certificate of incorporation, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Chelsea Neighborhood Center: correspondence, 1966-67, 1970, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Chelsea Save Our Homes and Business Committee: printed material, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Chelsea Strivers: correspondence, n.d. (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Chelsea Theater Center: correspondence, 1967-68 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Children to Palestine: program, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Chilmark Associates, Martha's Vineyard, [see also SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIAL and SERIES VIII. PHOTOGRAPHS]
    - Correspondence (includes Stanley King, Amherst College President; John P. Roche, Special Assistant to Pres. Johnson; Ralph Brown of Yale and ACLU; James McGregor Burns)
      - 1928-65 (Box 34, Folder 21-25)
      - 1966-70 (Box 35, Folder 1-3)
    - Legal matters
      - Rights of Way, 1930-1964 (Box 35, Folder 4-5)
      - Titles and Declarations of Trust, 1919-1958, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Reports, 1919-1965 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Annual meetings: minutes, 1921-1971 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Treasurer: reports, 1923-63 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Trustees: agendas, contracts, correspondence, financial statements, lists, and memoranda, 1964-68 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Christian Action: newsletters, 1954 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Churches, misc.: correspondence and programs, 1951-67 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Citizens Committee on American Policy in the Near East: correspondence, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Citizens Committee for Improved Public Transportation: correspondence, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Citizens Committee for Medicaid: correspondence, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Citizens Committee to Support the G.E. Strikers: correspondence and printed material, 1970. (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Citizens Committee for Voluntary Hospital Employees: correspondence, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Citizens Opposed to the New Constitution: correspondence, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Citizen's Union of the City of New York
    - General, 1960-1970 (Box 36, Folder 10-11)
    - Committees
      - Ethics: correspondence, minutes, notes, printed material, and reports, 1954-64, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Methods of Judicial Selection: agendas, correspondence, membership lists, minutes, notes, pamphlets, publicity, and reports, 1953, 1961-1969, n.d. (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - Steering: calendars, lists, minutes, printed material, and reports, 1964-70 (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - Subcommittee on Community Development: agendas, correspondence, lists, minutes, notes, and printed material, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - "Towards Better Judges"
        - Correspondence, 1960-64 (Box 36, Folder 16-17)
        - Proposals, publicity, and reports, 1960-62 (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
    - Publications
      - "A Citizens Guide to Gun Control," 1968 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - "Towards Better Judges," 1961 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - City Affairs Committee of New York: Report on the Seabury Investigation, 1933 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - City Planning Commission: correspondence, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Clinton Planning Council, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Committee to Abolish the House Un-American Activities Commission: correspondence and newspaper clipping, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Civil Rights in Metropolitan New York: correspondence, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Committee for Community Action: newspaper clipping, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Committee for Constitutional Reform: correspondence, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Committee to Defend America by Aiding the Allies: correspondence, 1940, [see also McCarthy hearings] (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Free Elections in the Dominican Republic: correspondence, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Committee for Gracie Mansion: correspondence, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Committee for Legal Abortion: correspondence and reports, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Committee on National Affairs: petition, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Committee on Women in World Affairs: description, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Community Corporation of the Lower West Side, [see Lower West Side Community Development Activities] (Box 37)
  - Community Progress Committee, [see Lower West Side Community Development Activities] (Box 37)
  - Conference of Commissions on the Status of Women: agenda, correspondence, and travel voucher, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Conference on Economic Progress: correspondence (Leon Keyserling), 1964 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Conference Group of U.S. National Organizations on the United Nations: correspondence, 1963-65 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Conference on the Status of Soviet Jews: correspondence (includes letters from Norman Thomas and Martin Luther King Jr.), 1964-66 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Congress of Racial Equality: correspondence (James Farmer), 1963 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Congressional Leadership for the Future: correspondence, 1970-71 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Consumers' Cooperative Services: minutes and newsletter, 1942-48 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Cosmopolitan Club: correspondence, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Council for the New York State College of Home Economics: minutes, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Council on Religion and International Affairs: correspondence, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Courts Committee of Women Lawyers: meeting schedule, 1924 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Democratic County Committee of New York: correspondence, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Democratic National Committee: clipping, 1940 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Democratic Party of New York County: designating petitions, 1967, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Democratic Voters Association: correspondence, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Descendants of the American Revolution: correspondence, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Eastern Sociological Society: program, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Electoral campaigns: printed material and publicity, 1952-69, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Elliot-Chelsea Nautical Cadets: newsletter, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Elliot-Chelsea Tenants Organization: correspondence, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Encampment for Citizenship: correspondence, 1964-66 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Euthanasia Educational Fund: correspondence, 1939 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Euthanasia Society of America: correspondence and newsletter, 1960, 1964-65, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation: clipping, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - Fort Hood Three Defense Committee: correspondence (from A.J. Muste), 1966 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - Friends Committee on National Legislation: correspondence, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - General Federation of Women's Clubs: pamphlet, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - German Exchange Program--U.S. State Department: correspondence (Ruth Woodsmall), grant application, and reports, 1949-50 (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - Girl Scout Council of Greater New York: correspondence and reports, 1964-71 (Box 37, Folder 46)
  - GRIPE (National Grass Rooters Interested in Poverty Elimination): correspondence and proposal, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - The Group: schedules, 1944, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 48)
  - Hill Club: correspondence and membership list, 1923, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 49)
  - Housing and Development Administration: press release, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 50)
  - Hudson Guild, [see Lower West Side Community Development Activities] (Box 37)
  - Inter-American Association for Democracy and Freedom: correspondence, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 51)
  - Inter-American Commission of Women
    - Correspondence and memoranda, 1945-47, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Printed material, 1948-50, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Report: "The Nationality of Women," 1948 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Inter Church Center: directory, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Institute of International Relations: conference proceedings, directory, and printed material, 1947 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - International Alliance of Women: correspondence and printed material, 1960-68 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - International Alliance of Women for Suffrage and Equal Citizenship: correspondence, 1943 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - International Cooperative Alliance: correspondence, 1944 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - International Development Conference: announcement and correspondence, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - International Federation of University Women: correspondence, 1951-53 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - International League for the Rights of Man: notes and program, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Iota Tau Tau: correspondence, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Japan International Christian University Foundation, Inc.: correspondence, 1963-69 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Jazz Arts Society: newsletter, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Jewish Labor Committee--Women's Division: conference program, 1950 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Joint Committee of American Agencies on Human Rights: minutes, 1946-50 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - La Guardia Memorial Association: correspondence, 1963-67 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Labor Club: program, 1939 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Law Students Civil Rights Research Council: correspondence, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Lawyers Committee on American Relations towards Vietnam: correspondence, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Lawyers Committee on American Relations with Spain: correspondence, 1939 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Lawyers Constitutional Defense Committee: correspondence, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - League for Industrial Democracy: correspondence and programs, 1951, 1955, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - League for Mutual Aid: agendas, correspondence, printed material, and programs, 1960-71 (Box 39, Folder 1-7)
  - League of Nations, [see also SERIES VIII. PHOTOGRAPHS]
    - General: printed material, 1937-39, 1945 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Committee for the Study of the Legal Status of Women
      - Overview: background information and founding documents, 1938 (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence
        - General, 1937-45 (Box 39, Folder 10-13)
        - Individuals, [see also United Nations correspondence]
          - Mary Anderson, 1938-40 (Box 40, Folder 1)
          - Margery Corbett Ashby, 1938 (Box 40, Folder 2)
          - Carrie Chapman Catt, 1938 (Box 40, Folder 3)
          - Cordell Hull, 1938 (Box 40, Folder 4)
          - Mary van Kleeck, 1938 (Box 40, Folder 5)
          - Ruth Woodsmall, 1938, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Minutes, 1938-39 (Box 40, Folder 7-8)
      - Publicity: press releases and statements, 1938-40 (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - Research and reports
        - Statements and Communications from Governments and International Women's Organizations, 1935-36 (Box 40, Folder 10)
        - Reports (Box 40, Folder 11-12)
        - Reports supplied by Women's Bureau of U.S., 1939 (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - Subjects
        - Economic policies: printed material, 1944 (Box 41, Folder 1)
        - Peace: lists, petitions, and printed material, 1937-43, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 2)
        - Women's work: printed material, 1936 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Travel arrangements: contacts, correspondence, reservations, and receipts, 1938-39 (Box 41, Folder 4-5)
  - League of Women Voters: clippings, correspondence, and programs, 1948-66, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Legal Aid Society: fundraising contact sheets, and correspondence, 1965-67 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Legal Defense Fund: correspondence, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Library Associates of Brooklyn College: constitution, map, and membership list, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Lower West Side Anti-Poverty Board, [SEE Lower West Side Community Development Activities] (Box 41)
  - Lower West Side Community Development Activities, [see also SERIES VIII. PHOTOGRAPHS]
    - Chelsea Committee for Neighborhood Development: agendas, correspondence, memoranda, proposals, and reports, 1960-70 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Chelsea Independent Anti-poverty Action Committee: description, and correspondence, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Community Corporation of the Lower West Side
      - Predecessors
        - Community Progress Committee
          - Overview: budget, bylaws, and publicity, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 12)
          - Correspondence, 1966-67 (Box 41, Folder 13)
          - Memoranda, 1966-67 (Box 41, Folder 14)
          - Minutes, 1965-67 (Box 41, Folder 15)
          - Grievances
            - General, 1967-70, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 16)
            - Jack Bordelay case: correspondence, memoranda, and newspaper clippings, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 17)
          - Procedures: correspondence and manual, 1966-67 (Box 41, Folder 18)
          - Programs: budgets, descriptions, proposals, and printed material, 1965-68, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 1)
          - Publicity and outreach: newspaper clippings and press releases, 1966-67, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 2)
          - Reports, 1966-67, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 3-4)
        - Lower West Side Anti-Poverty Board, Inc.
          - Overview: budget, by-laws, certificate of incorporation, newspaper clippings, and publicity, 1965-66, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 1)
          - Correspondence (John Kenneth Galbraith), 1965-66 (Box 43, Folder 2-3)
          - Minutes, 1965-66, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 4)
          - Memoranda, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 5)
          - Procedures, 1964-66, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 6)
          - Proposals and Reports
            - General, 1965-67, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 7)
            - Mitchel Sviridoff reports, vols. I and II, 1966-67 (Box 43, Folder 8)
          - Community Action Program: application, lists, notes, and printed material, 1964-66 (Box 43, Folder 9)